Lands' End All-American Quilt Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Contest Winners 1992, 1994, 1996, Some "slides" and "negatives" may be "positive transparencies." (Box 149-154)
  - 1996 Winners (Box 153-154)
    - 1996 Wyoming Winner: Jones, Heather. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9112)
Lammey, Philippa
Williston, Dorothy
District of Columbia
None
Florida
Adams, Connie
Ferguson, Vera
Haywood, Dixie
Patterson, Verna
Schwartz, Ellen
Willhoite, Jessie
Zoltai, Elva
Georgia
Osteen, Jack
Prewitt, Floy
Simpson, Sammie
Hawaii
Cox, Beverly
Dannells, Vernyce
Idaho
Hegg, Mary
Illinois
Belshe, Bonnie
Chickerneo, Connie
Schuler, Joan
Stinson, Charles
Indiana
Boomershire, Michael
Dintaman, Rosalie
Peppler, Susan
Stephan, Mary
Vandevoorde, Wilhelmina
Wildeman, Cecelia
Iowa
Johnson, Viola
McIlrath, Patricia
Kansas
Barker, Cheryl
Campbell, Elsie
Grigsby, Annette
Klueber, Kathleen
Scott, Elaine
Yeager, Juanita
Kentucky
Keller, Shari
Setmore, Inez
Louisiana
Mott, Virginia
Suydam, Sharon
Vandyne, Clarida
Maine
None
Maryland
Homewood, Carol
Rahl, Berice
Massachusetts
Barss, Sara
Small, Connie
Wirkkala, Laura
Woodburn, Jane
Michigan
Bloomensaat, Laura
Gillette, Marcia
Hallock, Susan
Powers, Karen
Robbins, Emma
Roossien, Sylvia
Stanley, Jackie
Wiegland, Patricia
Witting, Angie
Minnesota
Aul, Dorothy
Dobbs, Nell
Hedin, Susan
Knapp, Janet
McCarthy, Kay
Sells, Audree
Mississippi
Bass, Mabel
Dahlem, Emma
Howell, Olivia
Missouri
Alley, Irma
Danker, Lucile
Feldmann, Evelyn
Leith, Carrye
Nehring, Mary
Reynolds, James
Sanders, Marjorie
Wehmeyer, Sue
Yates, Judy
Montana
None
Nebraska
Burge, Shellly
Trizila, Marion
Turi, Gail
Nevada
Adams, Linda
New Hampshire
Calistro, ?
Conivay, Susan
Harvest, Cathryn
McDonough, Rita
Seipt, Corliss
New Jersey
Harman, Terry
Keera, Randy
Kurjian, Judith
Larson, Susan
Snyder, Elsie
Zucconi, Rosemary
New Mexico
Spargo, Dora
New York
Almann, Edith
Habecker, Loretta
Prindle, Cathleen
Schlegel, Nancy
Tadross, Marilyn
North Carolina
Boswell, Connie
Canhill, Linda
Graham, Leigh
Newton, Betty
Turner, Ginny
Winborne, Bernice
Wortman, Penelope
North Dakota
Troftgruben, Martha
Ohio
Barr, Ginny
Dickey, Evelyn
McClarren, Evelyn
Sweeney, Ellen
Wackenheim, Joann
Oklahoma
Greenlee, Gloria
Lutz, Jolene
Oregon
Hoadley, Eileen
Hoevet, Marne
Lake, Donna
Shipley, Grace
Pennsylvania
Crise, Joan
Kundrats, Sylvia
Nolt, Esther
Rickart, Geraldine
Rhode Island
None
South Carolina
Barber, Barbara
Brumbaugh, Elizabeth
Moody, Lillian
Nichols, Virginia
Smiley, Jan
South Dakota
Graber, Gertie
Pearson, Deborah
Jones, Linda
Lake, Beulah
Muntzing, Ruth
Tennessee
Armstrong, Patricia
Brickley, Lois
Sherrell, Marcia
Spicer, Mary
Texas
Brodie, Cindy
Fitzpatrick, Jeannette
Graves, Laura
Hartnell-Williams, Janet
Snow, Lanell
Taylor, Pam
Utah
Bentley, Carol
Charlesworth, Carol
Felsch, Kellee
Sullivan, Mary Kay
Vermont
Fisher, Emma
Hazen, Janet
Sargent, Freda
Virginia
Dieffenbacher, Ruth
Humphries, Suzanne
Lewis, Christine
Morris, Gay
Washington
Longenecker, Janet
Margaret, Patricia
Owings, C.
Sogn, Judy
Thoma, Frances
West Virginia
Aikman, Marilyn
Wisconsin
Hoffman, Annette
Johnson, Phyllis
Kaster, Bonnie
Mau, Marjorie
Temby, Judy
Trumpy, Betty
Wyoming
Amundson, Marta
Ruddy, Kris
1994 FINALISTS
Alabama
Callahan, Jane
Grafton, Sharron
Wascomb, Margaret
Alaska
Avara, Gwen
Dixon, Joann
Arizona
Paugh, Joan
Arkansas
Fredrick, Bonnie
Hale, Carmen
California
Brown, Nancy S.
Dabbs, Christine
Davis, Toni
Hansen, Cheri
Kent, Kay
Kitchen, Peggy
Colorado
Dimmock, Mary Beth
Foss, Irene M.
Mac Queen, Kathy
Peck, Judith
Ragan, Susan Swartz
Connecticut
Johnson, Gertrude
Lack, Caroline
McKinniss, Deborah Allen
Delaware
O'Day, Margaret
District of Columbia
None
Florida
Edwards, Patricia
Leavins, Varine
Lupkiewicz, Anna
MacLennand, Sara Ann
Watts, Audrey
Georgia
Analla, Wendy
Morris, Shelby
Hawaii
Kress, Fay
Seidel, Robert F.
Idaho
Mackowiak, Deonne
Stewart, Linda Brooks
Wilson, Leslie A.
Illinois
Bird, Arlen
Burdin, Diane
Burgess, Arene W.
Kickertz, Brenda
Kinka, Chris
Wedel, Lesley
Indiana
Harvey, Martha
Horn, Mary Kay
Palmiter, Kathy
Pharr, Neva
Iowa
Boehnke, Laura
Dunsdon, Alice
Gray, Linnea
Kerrigan, Kris
McPherson, Margaret
Scheib, Cheri Tice
Shoemaker, Marcia
Kansas
Cronhardt, Beth
Meyer, Ruth
Thompson, Terry Clothier
Kentucky
Brown, Nina
Piland, Virginia
Rosing, Dee
Louisiana
Monteith, Lisa
Rogers, Peggy
Sartin, Syble Magee
Maine
Massie, Mary A.
Trent, Claudia
Turcotte, Linda
Weaver, Julie
Maryland
Ashton, Lisa A.
Reddy, R. Mala
Scrivens, Jacqueline A.
Massachusetts
Bawn, Rosemary
Hamilton, Helen
Hibbert, Lynn
Patoka, Jude
Vachino, Gloria
Michigan
Bornsheuer, Carol Droll
Fante, Elizabeth
Poit, Linda
Poit, Linda
Minnesota
Benson, Karen
Beres, Catherine
Pierce, Kristi
Weigt, Bridget
Mississippi
Fiet, Tish
Nelson, Fae
Missouri
Carel, Teresa
Colvin, Donna
Lenz, Betty A.
Montana
Heine, Laura
Storholm, Emmy W.
Nebraska
Haubold, Linda
McIntyre, Sue
Meagher, Judy Girard
Nevada
Muri, Cheryl
New Hampshire
Corliss, Harriet
De Prima, Helen
Gollihue, Lisa
New Jersey
Ambrosio, Pam
Barry, Carol
Berenotto, Betty
Tornello, Lisa
New Mexico
Arseneault, Nancy
New York
Dunn, Frances
Hall, Linda
Sienk, Karen Hull
Wirchansky, Mary
North Carolina
Gabriel, Patricia Mullins
Lane, Susanna
Mendenhall, Irene
Schwartz, Rebecca
Tew, Harriet
North Dakota
Albrecht, Jackie
Ohio
Brunyate, Dorothy
Davis, Mary Ann
Elevick, Helen
Schaublin, Ruth
Sweeney, Ellen
Taylor, Joy
Oklahoma
Bryant, Pauline
Meetze, Janette
White, John W.
Oregon
Hoffman, Midge
Hutton, Terri
Kroft, June
Ortner, Joetta
Schweitzer, Marie
Pennsylvania
Albert, Donna
Adams, Nancy Becker
Eichner, Betty
Femia, Donna
Roan, Nancy
Rhode Island
Shapiro, Wendy
Timby, Deborah Bird
South Carolina
Boyson, Jean
Hewitt, Dora
Tobin, Dolores
South Dakota
Stearns, JoAnn
Tennessee
Eidson, Myrtle
Pickett, Frieda
Skelton, Nancy
Stoddart, Louise
Thomas, Ruby M.
Texas
Latimer, Carol
Orgish, Bea
Patterson, Lee
Welsch, Lynn B.
Utah
Caldwell, Nena
Seely, Ann
Vermont
Chutter, Aileen
Fisher, Emma
Moore, Pamela Allison
Virginia
Chase, Mary E.
Radcliff, M. Laurence
Washington
Nagler, Patricia
Perisho, Caroline
Simmons, Lorraine E.
Snapper, Audrey E.
West Virginia
Jackson, Lola
Jones, Nellie
Moore, Sheryl
Wisconsin
Abernathy, Joyce
Carroll, Eunice
Hart, Lois
Mirr, Eileen M.
Rouse, Kathryn
Wichman, Mildred
Wyoming
Hipol, Mary J.
Llaury, Caesha
1996 FINALISTS
Alabama
Naugher, Gayle
Taylor, Barbara
Alaska
Clouatre, Maxine S.
Gant, Alice
Hand, Susan
Nancarrow, Ree
Arizona
Duffy, Mattie
Hansen, Ruth
Kressge, Patricia
Rivera, Mary Lou
Zelnis, Evaleah
Arkansas
Hattaway, Cessarina
California
Boorman, Donna
Coscarelli, Jane
Francis, Colleen
Orndorff, Darla
McClellan, Winifred
Reutgen, Margaret
Rinderknecht, Margrit
Colorado
Beebe, Patricia
Broshous, Barbara
Broūn, Virginia
Hubbard, Patricia
McCollum, Janet
Vogel, Carole
Connecticut
Ryan, Bethany
Smith, Sandra
Delaware
None
District of Columbia
None
Florida
Davison, Nancy
Denenberg, Rita
Fink, Adeline
Herrington, Jan
Myers, Dorothy
Georgia
Harned, Patricia
Myers, Sandy Wise
Hawaii
Nakai, Cynthia
Van Der Horst, Rozemaryn
Idaho
Brooks, Kim
Ross, Carolynn
Wilson, Theresa
Illinois
Bird, Arlen
De La Cruz, Sharon
Haller, Robin
Lau, Betty Jane
Indiana
Kreider, Marianna
Rakowski, Mona
Iowa
Armstrong, Marjorie
Belling, JoAnn
Bullerman, Judy
Kansas
Bauer, Marge
Bauer, Sharon
Matthews, Maralee
Kentucky
Cason, Anna
Hill, Chizuko
Humphries, Pauline
Humphrey, Georgia
Lamb, Connie
Rosing, Dee
Wolf, Doris
Louisiana
Hatten, Patsy
Johnson, Janet
Maine
None
Maryland
McWilliams, Margaret
Massachusetts
None
Mississippi
Johnson, Elizabeth
Salvucci-Guerini, J.
Michigan
Florida, Mary
Mayo, Kathleen
Wierda, Laura
Minnesota
Crookston, Gayle
Galliford, Suzanne
Murray, Laura
Pollard, Mimie
Rinck, Leslie
Mississippi
Johnson, Clara
Nicholson, Naomi
Missouri
Braig, Carole
Struckhoff, Deborah
Montana
Badgett, Gloria
Nebraska
Phipps, Glenda
Stengel, Gwen
Nevada
Colyer, Lisa
New Hampshire
Gebo, Sandi
Messier, Anne-Marie
New Jersey
Gould, Sandra
Sarafine, Pearl
New Mexico
Trujillo, Mary Lou
New York
Friedman, Stacey
Ink, Lynn
Sharrow, Irene
Sickler, Christine
Tennyson, Kathryn
Yorinks, Adrienne
North Carolina
Duske, Ruth
North Dakota
Joos, Lori
Ohio
Conant, Elizabeth
Hubbard, Eilene
Kelley, Beverly
Martinez, Valerie
Melrose, Beverly
Null, Nancy
Ricker, Donna
Oklahoma
Thomas, Pam
Oregon
Davis, Judith
Pennsylvania
Everett, Cassandra
Faggerty, Sandra G.
Hazel, Irene
McDonough, Letty
Pritts, Fay
Stoltz, Linda
Rhode Island
None
South Carolina
Bagdan, Karen
Kessler, Ilse
South Dakota
Christophersen, Darlene
Tennessee
Holt, Joyce
Texas
Ewing, Katharine
Gadbois, Henri
Reed, Donna
Sherrill, Alma
Wyatt, Marcia
Utah
Weeks, Helen
Vermont
Cameron, Monica
Virginia
Calhoun, Francis
Hanson, Kay
Robertson, C. Ann
Washington
Chapman, Marie
Obermiller, Darcel
West Virginia
None
Wisconsin
Kroth, Pat
Lauchart, Rose
Libert, Sharon R.
Wyoming
Gorges, Barb
Appendix B: Quilt Types in the Collection
album quilts
Baltimore album quilts
Amish quilts
African American quilts
hand appliqué quilts
machine appliqué
cathedral window quilts
children's quilts
crazy quilts
crib quilts
double wedding ring quilts
embroidered quilts
fancy work quilts
foundation piecing quilts
friendship quilts
grandmother's flower garden quilts
handkerchief quilts
Irish chain quilts
log cabin quilts
memory quilts
needlework quilts
nine patch quilts
original design quilts
patchwork quilts
photo quilts
sampler quilts
scrap quilts
story quilts
string quilts
strip quilts
Sunbonnet Sue quilts
t-shirt quilts
trapunto quilts
wall quilts
watercolor quilts